we have seen that filters and effects
我们已经看到滤镜和特效
must be rasterized to be visible in a
必须栅格化才能在
PDF also when importing an SVG and
PDF在导入SVG时也是如此
scribus you will not see the blur effect
Scribus你不会看到模糊效果
you'll see the original Vector shape but
您将看到原始的矢量形状，但是
effects like blur are emitted so artwork
像模糊这样的效果被发射出来，所以图稿
often must be rasterized to be visible
通常必须栅格化才能显示
in other programs the two most used bit
在其他程序中，两个最常用的位
map formats are PNG and jpeg jpeg
地图格式为png和jpeg jpeg。
doesn't support transparency so
不支持透明度，所以
transparent areas will be filled in with
透明区域将使用
white also jpeg uses a lossy compression
White Jpeg也使用有损压缩
algorithm sacrificing image quality so
算法以牺牲图像质量为代价
PNG is higher quality and the best
PNG质量更高，是最好的
choice for everything except photographs
除了照片，什么都可以选择
let's see how to save this logo as a bit
让我们看看如何将此徽标保存为
map I will save one for the internet and
地图我会留一张放在网上
one for print what we will see is that
一种是印刷的，我们将看到的是
you always save in pixels I go to file
你总是以像素为单位保存我要保存的文件
export I see I can save the entire page
导出我知道我可以保存整个页面
when I click on document I see the area
当我单击文档时，我会看到该区域
that will be exported comprises the
将被导出的内容包括
visible elements I only want to export
我只想导出的可见元素
the logo so I drag over the logo then I
所以我把徽标拖到上面然后我
go to selection now I see the export
现在转到选择，我将看到导出
area is confined to the selection the
区域仅限于所选的
logo for the website has to be 200
该网站的标志必须是200
pixels high so for height I give in 200
像素高，所以我给的高度是200
when I press enter I see the width is
当我按Enter键时，我看到宽度是
automatically set to 175 pixels DPI is
自动设置为175像素DPI是
unrelated to pixel dimensions changing
与像素尺寸变化无关
the DPI will also change the amount of
DPI还将更改
pixels so I leave DPI as it is I click
像素，所以我让DPI保持不变，然后单击
on export selected only I click on
仅在选择导出时，我单击
select export format and choose PNG at
选择导出格式并在以下位置选择PNG
the right are different options I prefer
右边是我更喜欢的不同选项
compression on nine to get the smallest
在9号上压缩，得到最小的
file size and anti-alias should be on
应启用文件大小和消除锯齿
two anti-alias on zero gives ragged
零上的两个反走样给了参差不齐的
edges click on the folder icon to choose
边单击文件夹图标以选择
a location to save then click on export
要保存的位置，然后单击导出
when I open the PNG and gim I see the
当我打开PNG和GIM时，我看到
size is 175 x 200 pixels now let's save
大小是175x200像素，现在让我们节省
the logo for print for print you also
用于打印的徽标也可打印
save in pixels this is because 300
以像素为单位进行存储这是因为300
pixels is the same as 1 in let's say my
像素等于1，假设我的
logo has to be 2 1/2 in high so 2 1/2 *
徽标必须高2 1/2，因此2 1/2 *
300 pix is 750 pixels so for height I
300像素是750像素，因此对于高度我
give in
屈服
750 when I press tab width is
当我按下标签宽度时，750
automatically calculated to 657 pixels I
自动计算为657像素I
see the DPI value has also changed again
看到DPA值也又变了
in this situation the DPI value is
在这种情况下，DPA值为
unrelated to the pixel dimensions the
与像素尺寸无关
only time you use the DPI value field is
只有当您使用DPA值字段时
on the page tab this is because a page
在页面选项卡上，这是因为页面
has a concrete Dimension like A4 to
具有像A4这样的具体维度，
export a page for print you set it to
将您设置为的页面输出以进行打印
DPI changing the DPI change the pixel
DPA改变DPA改变像素
dimensions now we can see that an A4 is
维度现在我们可以看到A4是
2,480 x 358 pixels for print
2，480 x 358像素用于打印